Antonio Ruiz

devtoti.vercel.app

(C) devtoti

\$\&\ +52 55 4831 8571

Front-End Designer, Illustrator and Architect based in Mexico City. Strong passion for building unique web applications and UI's according to web standards with a human-centered design approach. Teamwork oriented with a particular interest in ensuring aesthetically pleasing user experiences.

Career History

Independent creator

Jul. 2019 - now

Front-End Designer

- Design multiple webpages and applications from scratch in HTML5, CSS3 and JS
- Build web-apps mockups in Figma and Illustrator for better accessibility and user interactions
- Code responsive landing pages and animations based on design patterns and guidelines

Freelancing, Fiverr International Ltd.

Sep. 2021 - now

Professional Illustrator

- Develop digital art and illustrations for online publishing purposes
- Design several logos, banners, headers and landing pages for different startups

CECOFARQ, UNAM

Aug. 2020 - Dec. 2021

Computer Lab Supervisor & Professor Asistant

- Taught design principles and 3D Modeling best practices to sophomore architecture students
- Mantained online platforms and launched intensive and advanced AutoCAD and Revit courses
- Supervised student use of computing equipment and ensured that lab guidelines were followed

Residencial Loma Diamante

Aug. 2017 - Feb. 2022

Architectural Draftsman / Apprenticeship

- Created the leading designs for a real estate company based in Mexico City
- Developed multiple architectural projects with computer assisted programs
- Built 3D models and custom website templates for online publishing purposes

Qualifications

• HTML5 • Reactjs • Photoshop • Sass

CSS3
Nextjs
Illustrator
Bootstrap

• JavaScript • Figma • InDesign • Version Control (Git)

Education

Universidad Nacional Autónoma de México, CDMX

B.A. in Architecture

Aug. 2016 - Dec. 2021